Hello and welcome back
Let's dive into everything this course has in store
Google kick things off with introduction
We cannot discuss why moving beyond the default selenium library is beneficial
Then we will explore what selenium base is and how it stands out compared to the standard selenium
Following that we'll see how brightest Works in tandem with selenium base
After laying the groundwork we will jump into setting up our envir
We'll start by installing Python and setting up by
Covering both Macos and window
We will discuss the importance of virtual environment
And get everything ready to install selenium base
Then comes the exciting
Which is writing our first
Will get grips with the test
Next understand how it operates
And how differs from selenium
Will intentionally fill a test to examine the assertions and error
Only on we will push a changes to GitHub which is crucial for tracking progress in your project
As you become a doctor crafting basic
Will dive into selenium base command
Will cover range of assertions provided by selenium bass and pee test
Followed by a deep dive into weight
Including the commonly used implicit and explicit
Next we'll tackle different web elements like sliders
Please drop
Is checkbox iframes and more
It will also learn to open an interact with new
From there we will discover how to upload file
Both individually and in batch
Will explore how to manage file Parts effectively for file upload
As we grow comfortable with testing will start building a framework
Beginning with the page object model
Converting existing test and setting up a config
Will also integrate winter and file formatter into a framework
Then we going to move on to some Advanced topics
That is how you can go ahead and optimize your framework
We will do that by using hug
Data driven
And utility
Will you find a test as well as a framework
We will also learn how to execute the selectively focusing on specific groups
Excluding others as needed
When is Spotify Advanced concept we're going to take a look at how we can
Play skilled the framework
This is where we will Embrace parallel testing cross browser testing and headless run
Who
Speed and efficiency
Then we're going to move on to debug
This is where we going to cover the Bas
And learn about PDP Trace mode
Before moving on to more Advanced Techniques such as with by John Denver
Then we will take a look at how to review and generate insightful reports
Including selenium bass Auto generated logs and dashboard
Additionally we will also see how we can combine Parts HTML reports
With the selenium is Dash
Singapore's final stages will integrate a
Cast with Seattle
Will set up linters and format
All of that as part of a CF pipal
Then we will bring browserstack into the mix for Crossroads the testing as well as cross device
And to tie all of it together we going to integrate GitHub actions with browser
Connect for the seamless end to end testing
As you can tell we have a lot to cover over here
But rest assured for the schools I will be here to provide personal support whenever you need it
Ensuring you get the most out of your
I hope you're excited to start this journey as I am